♪ It seems today that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
♪ Family Guy 10x16 ♪ Killer Queen
杀手女王
片名来自皇后乐队的同名歌曲
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
晚上好 Quahog 我是Tom Tucker
Good evening, Quahog. I'm Tom Tucker.
今晚的头条新闻：
Our top story tonight:
一个令人震惊的事件
In a shocking turn of events,
底特律城被正式放弃了
the city of Detroit has officially given up.
没歇根州首府 汽车之城
在衰败后一直想恢复繁荣
现在前任市长已将城市之匙
The now former mayor has given the key to the city
市长是NBA50大巨星之一的戴夫·宾
交还给了休伦湖印第安部落
back to the Huron Indian tribe.
那么 永别了 底特律
So, farewell, Detroit.
出自Bob Seger对Axel Foley所说的话 我们从没真正在乎过 Joyce
From Bob Seger to Axel Foley, we never really cared. Joyce?
前者为密歇根州摇滚歌手
后者为艾迪墨菲在《比佛利山超级警探》中扮演的角色
谢谢 Tom 本地消息
Thanks, Tom. In local news,
Quahog本周末将迎来一位特殊的客人
Quahog is expecting a special guest this weekend,
著名的亚洲大胃王比赛冠军
famed Asian competitive eating champion
查尔斯·山本
Charles Yamamoto.
山本至今未输过一场吃热狗比赛
Yamamoto has not yet lost a hot dog eating competition
游遍世界无敌手
on his world tour.
不过要是你觉得自己有点本事
But if you think you have what it takes
能够打败世上最厉害的大胃王
to beat the best eater in the world,
请于本周六前往James Woods高中停车场
come down to the James Woods High parking lot this Saturday
带上50块报名费 和大胃口吧
with $50 and a large appetite.
哇 也许你应该参加比赛 老爸
Wow, maybe you should enter the contest, Dad.
我敢说你会赢
I'll bet you could win.
好吧 我会的 Chris
Well, I would, Chris,
如果我不是这么着迷于我现在身材的话
if I wasn't so obsessed with my figure.
哎对了
Wait a minute.
Chris 你有吃过什么东西吗
Chris, have you ever eaten anything?
只是 好像 从来没停过
Only, like, all the time!
太好了 那我们只需要弄50块钱
Perfect! Now we just need the 50 bucks.
真该死 我就知道不该为Mort命名那颗星星
Damn it, I knew I shouldn't have named that star for Mort.
呃 把钱给我吧
Ugh! Just give me the money.
Peter 我们才不会花50块钱
Peter, we're not spending $50
让Chris的两颊塞满热狗
so Chris can stuff his face with hot dogs.
好吧 随你
All right, fine.
我会想办法自己弄到那笔钱
I'll figure out a way to get the cash myself.
我是个聪明人
I'm a smart guy.
Peter 不 你不是
Peter, no, you're not.
这下你不觉得自己很可笑吗
Don't you feel ridiculous now?
好吧 Chris 如果我们要支付比赛费
All right, Chris, if we're gonna pay the entry fee
参加大胃王比赛
for that eating contest,
只好卖掉我的一些旧藏货了
we got to sell some of my old stuff.
- 这些是什么 老爸 - 哇
- What are these, Dad? - Oh, wow.
我有很久没看到这些了
I haven't seen those in a while.
这是我珍藏的70年代《花花公子》旧杂志
Those are my old Playboys from the '70s.
老天啊 真是太性感了
Oh, my God, this one's so hot.
你差不多可以看到一点点女人
You can almost see a little bit of woman.
讽刺过去黄色杂志的女优都不流行剃毛
哇 Peter 你有一些很酷的唱片嘛
Wow, Peter, you've got some pretty cool albums here.
是啊 我以前可是个很酷的小肥仔呢
Yeah, well, I was one cool potato back in the day.
要知道 其中有一些可能很值点钱
You know, some of these might actually be worth something.
看这个——披头士 滚石
Look at this-- Beatles, Rolling Stones.
老天呐 我还从来没见过这个
Oh, my God, I haven't seen this one in forever.
看看这个 皇后乐队的"世界新闻"
Look-Look at this. Queen, News of the World.
英国摇滚乐队 经典作品有"We Are the Champions"
"we will rock you"等
你看看
Check it out.
啊
Aah!
怎么了
Oh, what's the matter?
这到底是什么东西 机器人杀手怪物
What the hell is that?! A killer robot monster?!
不 是"世界新闻"
No, it's News of the World.
是皇后乐队的一张唱片 看
It's an album by the band Queen. See?
啊 Stewie 别紧张
Aah! Stewie, relax.
不 Brian 把那东西给我拿远点
No, Brian! You keep that thing away from me!
它…它是不是在看着我
Is it... Is it looking at me?!
它能看到我吗
Can it see me?!
唉 你还真是害怕这东西 是吧
(laughing): Man, you're really scared of this thing, huh?
它会吃小男孩吗
Does it eat little boys?!
我不知道 也许 如果它饿了
I don't know. Maybe, if it's hungry.
给你50块 这张唱片我买了
Here's 50 bucks. I'm taking this album.
哇 你看呐 Chris
Oh, wow, check it out, Chris!
我们挣到了大胃王参赛费
We got our entry fee for the eating contest!
接下来的五天中
Now for the next five days,
我们一门心思只放在训练上
we're gonna focus on nothing but training.
破晓时分我们就起床
We'll even get up at the crack of dawn.
老爸
Dad?
老爸 该起床了
Dad, it's time to get up.
哎我靠 Chris 天才刚刚亮啊
Oh, jeez, Chris, it's the crack of dawn.
是的 可是老爸 是你让我叫醒你的
Yeah, but Dad, you said to wake you up.
是的…是的 可是 呃…
Yeah... Yeah, but, uh...
还是…进-进…进来…
Just... get-get... get in...
进被窝里来 跟你爹妈呆一起
get in the bed with me and your mom.
好的 可是训练怎么办
Okay, but what about training?
哦 你闻着就像融化的奶酪
Oh, you smell like melted cheese.
啧啧 啧啧 啧啧 啧啧 啧啧 啧啧
Yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy.
早上好 Rupert
Good morning, Rupert.
请告诉我你把咖啡机定好时间了
Please tell me you set the timer on the coffeemaker
因为我完全忘了
because I completely forgot.
你这个王八蛋
You son of a bitch!
早上好 希望我帮到你起床了
Good morning. Thought I'd help you wake up.
上帝 为什么他看着很悲伤
God, why does he look sad?!
他已经毁灭人类了啊
He's already destroyed mankind!
他还想要干什么
What else could he want?!
嗨 Carl
Hey, Carl.
嗨 能给我拿两张刮刮乐彩票吗
Hey, can I get a couple of scratch-off lottery tickets?
当然可以 Brian
Oh, sure, Brian.
唔 Brian 能让我刮一张吗 我喜欢刮彩票
Ooh, Brian, can I do one? I love scratchers!
好吧 就刮一张吧
Well, all right, maybe just one.
樱桃
Cherry.
又一个樱桃
Another cherry.
嗯 加油 再来一个 再来一个
Oh, come on, one more, one more!
谢了 Carl
Thanks, Carl.
呵呵 不用谢 挺有意思
Yeah, you're welcome. That was fun.
回见
See you later.
哎 谢谢你让我扮演尤达
Hey, uh, thanks for letting me be Yoda.
星战版FG中他扮演尤达大师
嗯
Yup.
这是什么
What is this?
(经典外国儿歌Pop Goes the Weasel)
呵-呵-呵 我怕什么呢
Oh-ho-ho, what was I worried about?
啊 啊 啊 上帝啊
Aah! Aah! Aah! Oh, God!
啊 啊
Aah! Aah!
他在流血呢 老兄
He's bleeding, man!
他在流血呢 没人采取任何措施
He's bleeding, and nobody's doing anything about it!
我来告诉你"世界新闻"是什么
I'll tell you what the news of the world is.
我们有TM大麻烦了
We're in a lot of (bleep) trouble!
好的 Chris 就是这儿
All right, Chris, this is it.
这就是我们奋斗的目标
This is what we've been working for.
如果你感觉紧张 就想象观众裸体的场景
If you get nervous, just picture the audience naked
让热狗滑进你的喉咙
and slide those hot dogs down your throat.
女士们先生们 欢迎
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome
来到"世界吃热狗冠军大赛"
to the World Hot Dog Eating Championship Competition!
有请我们战无不胜的冠军食客
Please welcome our undefeated champion eater,
查尔斯·山本
Charles Yamamoto!
괴물 = monster
老天呐 那家伙块头真大
Oh, my God, that guy is huge.
好的 食客们 你们有十分钟时间
All right, eaters, you have ten minutes.
各就各位 预备 开吃
On your marks, get set, eat!
加油 Chris 你做得很棒
Come on, Chris. You're doing great.
继续保持 你就要成功了
Just keep going. You're almost there.
好吧 我最好抓紧时间了
Well, I'd better get a move on.
时间快到了
Time's almost up!
比赛依然激烈紧张
It's gonna be a close one!
Chris 你还落后四个热狗
Chris, you're four hot dogs behind!
加油 赶快
Come on! Hurry!
呃 我吃不下去了
Oh! I can't eat anymore.
记得我怎么跟你说的
Remember what I told you.
我的液囊边上长了些奇怪的囊肿
I get these weird cyst things right on the fringe of my sac.
我想去检查一下
I want to get 'em checked,
但我又怕他们会告诉我什么恐怖的结果
but I'm afraid of what they're gonna tell me.
他说得对 我能做到
He's right. I can do it!
胜者已经决出
ANNOUNCER: We have a winner!
女士们先生们 山本终于被打败了
Ladies and gentlemen, Yamamoto has finally been defeated!
Chris 你成功了 你是冠军
Chris, you did it. You're a champion!
现在你也有了自己的粉丝后援团
And now you get your pick of the groupies.
她们真亮
They're shiny.
是啊 今天挺热的(胖子爱出汗啊...)
Yeah, it's a pretty warm day.
啊
Oh!
嗨 嗨 嗨 你好 冠军
Hey, hey, hey, there, champ!
啊 看看他 Lois
Aw, look at him, Lois.
大胜之后的小憩
Relaxing after his big victory.
Peter 他不是在休息
Peter, he's not relaxing.
他现在可疼的要命呢
He's in a great deal of pain.
该死 你没看到自己对他做了什么吗
Damn it, don't you see what you did to him?
我跟你说别带他去参加大胃王比赛
I told you not to take him to that eating competition,
可你却故意跟我对着干
and you deliberately defied me!
好吧 那你到底想怎样
All right, what's this really about?
Peter Chris已经超重了
Peter, Chris is already overweight.
我们得为他的健康负起责任来
We need to start taking responsibility for his health.
所以我决定为他报一个减肥训练营
So I decided to sign him up for fat camp.
什么 妈妈 我不想去什么减肥训练营
What?! Mom, I don't want to go to fat camp!
对不起 宝贝 这都是为了你自己好
I'm sorry, sweetie. It's for your own good.
相信我 你对自己的感觉会变好很多
And trust me, you'll feel much better about yourself.
每个人都想拿我寻开心
Everyone's gonna make fun of me!
唉 不会的 谁要拿你寻开心啊
Oh, come on, who's gonna make fun of you?
嗨 胖墩 我听说你要去减肥训练营
Hey, fatty, I hear you're going to fat camp.
那才是你该待的地方
That's where you belong!
Peter 别闹了
Peter, stop it!
最好别让我在舞会上看见你
And I'd better not see you at the big dance!
你 走了
Come on, you.
对不起 Chris 我得跟他去了
Sorry, Chris. I-I'm gonna go with him.
嗨 欢迎来到"新开始"训练营
Hi. Welcome to Camp Fresh Start.
嗯 我们的儿子太肥 所以就来了
Yeah, our son's gross, so here we are.
名叫Griffin
The name's Griffin.
啊 对 Chris Griffin
Ah, yes, Chris Griffin.
我们安排你住在花椰菜小屋中
We have you staying in the Broccoli Cabin.
这么说你们俩要把我丢在这儿了
So you guys are just gonna leave me here?
是的 宝贝 训练营就是这样
Yeah, honey. That's what camp is.
我不想留下来
I don't want to stay!
求你们带我回家
Please take me home!
我不想参加减肥训练营
I don't want to go to fat camp!
唉 别啊 Chris 你妈是对的
Aw, come on, Chris. Your mother's right.
这是为你好
This'll be good for you.
呃 那你为什么不必参加
Well, how come you don't have to go?!
你比我还要胖呢
You're fatter than I am!
哈 问得好 Peter
Huh. Good question, Peter.
为什么你不必参加
How come you don't have to go?
你们在说什么
What are you talking about?
呵呵 是你带他参加了
Well, you're the one who entered him
那个吃热狗大赛
in that hot dog eating contest.
而且 他说的也对
Besides, he's right.
你自己也好减掉点肥肉了
You could stand to lose a few pounds yourself.
除非你觉得自己做不到
Unless you don't think you could handle it.
哦 是吗
Oh, yeah?
好吧 我看我能行
Well, I think I can.
你说什么
What was that?
你别管我说什么
Never you mind what that was.
起床了 各位
Rise and shine, everyone!
你往里面藏什么
What do you got there?
糖块 是吗
A candy bar, huh?
还有其他违禁品吗
Got any other contraband?
- 没有 - 别跟我撒谎
- No. - Don't lie to me.
我爸曾做过律师
My father was a lawyer.
哦 那你爸就是让人高潮的咯(双关脱罪)
Oh, so your dad gets guys off.
Peter Griffin 本屋搞笑大王
Peter Griffin. Cabin clown.
你的包呢 胖子
Where's your bag, fatty?
欢迎你搜查我的"牛肉提箱"
You're welcome to search my "beef case."
谐音brief case公文皮包
但是里面什么"羊肉"都没有
But there's "mutton" in there.
谐音nothing
Peter Griffin 本屋搞笑大王
Peter Griffin. Cabin clown.
你麻烦大了 先生
You're in big trouble, mister.
哎哟 这家伙还真是明察秋毫 蒙骗不了
Oh, there's no pulling the wool over this guy's eyes.
字面意思为 拉过羊毛遮住你的眼
看来我得躲起来了
Looks like I'd better go on the "lamb."
字面意思为 去骑"羊羔"
Peter Griffin 本屋搞笑大王
Peter Griffin. Cabin clown.
我觉得自己在减肥营中能挺过去
I think I'm gonna do okay here at fat camp.
你确定你有这能耐?
You sure you got the "chops" for it?
字面意思为 你确定有排骨
闭嘴吧你 我才是本屋搞笑大王
Knock it off. I'm the cabin clown.
然后他走进厨房
And then he went into the kitchen,
慢慢打开了冰箱 竟然是空的
slowly opened the refrigerator, and it was empty!
于是 那个人
So then, the man,
饿得全身乏力 从冰箱那里冲到
weak with hunger, raced from the refrigerator
柜台前 想找份外卖菜单
to the counter to look for a delivery menu,
但他能找到的全都是素菜馆
but all he could find was one for a vegan place!
素菜馆不是真的 对吗
Vegan places aren't real, right?
不 他们是假的 还是真的呢
No, they're not real. Or are they?!
啊 沙拉
Aah! Salad!
感谢你的分享 Leonard
Thank you for sharing, Leonard.
我认为你过去得买张新沙发才是解决办法
And I think getting a new couch was the way to go.
谁还有什么故事
Is there someone else who has a story
要分享吗 Peter
they'd like to share? Peter?
呃 有 好的
Uh, yeah, sure.
有一次 我乘市内公交
This one time, I was on a city bus,
坐我旁边的家伙
and the guy next to me
在吃一桶炸鸡
was eating a bucket of fried chicken.
- 嗯 - 唔 好吃
- Mmm! - Ooh! Yum!
Peter左手边是AD中Steve的小胖子朋友Barry Robinson
那气味吸引了我 你们懂的
And the smell was getting to me, you know.
虽然我不认识那个人
And even though I didn't know the guy,
我就埋头凑上前
I just dug in
开始大口往嘴里填炸鸡
and started stuffing that chicken into my mouth.
啧啧 真囧啊
O-Oh! Embarrassing.
我吃完了
I've done that.
太好吃了
It was so delicious.
可是…那其实不是炸鸡
But... it wasn't fried chicken.
那是个婴儿
It was a baby!
It was a baby.
恶搞了电视剧《风流军医俏护士》中最终集的情节
Stewie?
Rupert 我们不会让那邪恶的机器人
Rupert, we won't give that evil robot
如愿以偿地杀掉我们
the satisfaction of killing us.
我们要用自己的方式一起上路
We'll go together on our own terms.
另一个世界再见了
See you on the other side.
我的天呐
Oh, my God!
Stewie 不
Stewie, no!
你脑子出什么毛病了
What the hell's wrong with you?!
因为那个机器人
It's that robot!
他杀了皇后乐队 现在他也要来杀我
He killed Queen, and now he's going to kill me!
他没有杀掉皇后乐队
He didn't kill Queen.
他们都好好活着呢
They're all fine.
大部分好好的
Most of them are fine.
乐队成员Freddie Mercury1991年死于艾滋病
听着 Stewie 我很抱歉吓到了你 好吗
Look, Stewie, I'm sorry for scaring you, all right?
可不至于吧 那又不是真的机器人
But come on, it's not a real robot.
看 这 这就是张唱片 你看
See? It, It's just an album. Look.
给 你想打它吗
Here, you want to hit it?
呃…我通常会对那些东西感觉舒服一些
Well... I'm usually more comfortable around things
如果他们能放进我嘴里的话
if I can put them in my mouth.
那么 我能把它放嘴里吗
So, can I put it in my mouth?
可以吧
I guess.
这就是张唱片啊
This is just an album!
是啊 我已经跟你说了
Yeah, that's what I've been trying to tell you.
那你会原谅我吗
So, you know, can you forgive me?
唉 我应该会的
Oh, I suppose so.
我是说 连麦哲伦都原谅了那个"陆地哟"的搞怪家伙
I mean, Magellan forgave the "Land Ho" prankster.
第一个发现了地球是圆的
陆地哟
Land ho!
在哪儿 在哪儿
Where?! Where?!
骗你的 傻了吧 撸瑟
Psych! Made you look, loser.
还好没有陆地
Good thing there wasn't land
不然你就得会见土著人
or else you'd have to meet the natives
- 并穿着这件沾有芥末污渍的上衣了 - 什么污渍
- with that mustard stain on your shirt. - What stain?
啊
Ah!
唉 我这趟旅程怎么就带上你了
Ugh! Why did I even bring you on this trip?!
因为老子是整个欧洲最好的
Because I'm the best damn land spotter
陆地眺望者
in all of Europe.
的确如此 你是最好的
It's true. You are the best.
嗯 我不需要你告诉我这个
Yeah, I don't need you to tell me that.
老爸 我再也走不动了
Dad, I can't take this anymore.
我又累又饿
I'm so tired and I'm so hungry.
我有个主意 Chris 跟我来
I got an idea, Chris. Follow me.
我们要去干嘛
What are we doing?
我曾经在一本书上见过这样的树林
I saw a forest like this in a book one time,
我知道在某个地方有一间姜饼屋
and I know there's a gingerbread house out here somewhere.
出自格林童话"汉赛尔与格莱特"
你觉得我们能找到它吗
Do you think we could find it?!
我们必须找到 Chris 我们-我们得吃点东西
We have to, Chris. We-we gotta eat something
不能光靠他们给我们吃的
besides what they're feeding us.
我明白你的意思 老爸
I know what you mean, Dad.
我饿得都能吃下这个死去的训练营员了
I'm so hungry I could eat this dead camper.
我靠
Holy crap!
好吧 很明显我们还没有收集到所有证据
Well, we clearly don't have all the evidence yet,
不过这从没有难倒过我们 对吗
but that's never stopped us before, right?
哦 这儿没有其他警察
Oh, there's no other cops here.
不过我们能确认一件事 这孩子是被谋杀的
But we do know one thing, this kid was murdered.
谋杀 这世上有谁
Murdered?! Who in the world
会去谋杀一个训练营员
would want to kill a camper?
别看我啊
Don't look at me.
我只是来这放下我儿子的
I'm just here to drop off my son.
《黑色星期五》系列中的杀人狂Jason
拥有不死之身 杀露营者出身
贾斯汀 贾斯汀 那么做对我不管用
Justin? Justin, that does not work for me.
而且看起来有外伤的痕迹
And it looks like there are signs of trauma
在喉咙附近
around the throat.
有人勒死了这个胖孩子
Somebody strangled this fat kid.
慢着 他是被勒死的
Wait. He was strangled?
嗯
Yeah.
Joe 我知道是谁干的了
Joe, I know who did it.
你知道 是谁
You do? Who?
嗯 我知道只有一个人
Well, there's only one person I know
热衷于勒死胖子：
who likes to strangle fat guys:
Patrick Pewterschmidt.
他是谁
Who's that?
我的大舅子
My brother-in-law.
江湖人称"胖子扼杀者"
People call him "The Fat Guy Strangler."
出自417 也是那集的片名
他一直对勒死胖人情有独钟
He's always had a thing for strangling fat guys.
我看他符合犯罪特征 Peter
I guess he fits the profile, Peter,
可是Lois的哥哥被锁在精神病院啊
but Lois's brother is locked up in an asylum.
好吧 不管怎样 我们得离开这里
Well, either way, we gotta get out of here.
不然 我们就成了"坐鸭"
Otherwise, we're just sitting ducks!
嗨 我们都知道这家伙想泡靓妹
Hey, we all know this guy goes for the classy ladies.
恶搞了喜剧中心的吐槽大会 吐槽者Jeff Ross尤其本人配音
参加过多届吐槽大会 正在吐槽"坐鸭"
事实上 我有次碰见他
In fact, I once caught him trying
在勾搭一个妓鸭
to pick up a quack whore.
好吧 别笑了
All right, calm down.
我们都有犯错的时候
We all make bad choices.
喂
Hello?
Lois 我希望你坐稳了
Lois, I hope you're sitting down.
我有事情要告诉你
I got something to tell ya.
天呐 出什么事了
Oh, God, what's wrong?
一切都还好吗 是Chris出事了吗
Is everything okay? Is it Chris?
不 我是Peter 你老公
No, it's Peter, your husband.
不过我打电话有要紧事说
But I'm calling with big news.
我在训练营饰演了
I was Anita in the camp production
《西城故事》里的安妮塔
of West Side Story.
Peter 你知道自己唱快节奏歌曲很糟糕的
Peter, you know you're terrible at patter songs.
我唱得还行呀
I did okay.
♪ (mumbles lyrics) ...America ♪
♪ (mumbles) ...America ♪
♪ (mumbling) ...America ♪
♪ (mumbling) ...America. ♪
我还有另一条消息
I got other news, too.
训练营有个胖孩子被勒死了
One of the fat kids at camp got strangled!
我的天呐
Oh, my God!
是的 不过别担心 不是你哥哥干的
Yeah, but don't worry. It ain't your brother.
他还锁在精神病院里
He's still locked up in that asylum.
呃 妈妈…
Um, Mom...
看看谁来拜访我们了
look who dropped by for a visit.
你好 Lois
Hello, Lois.
Patrick!
好久不见了
It's been a long time.
Peter 他在这儿呢
Peter, he's here!
哎对了 Lois 我想继续回到
Wait a second, Lois, I want to go back
你说我快歌唱不好的问题上来
to what you said about my patter singing.
你有什么资格说我
Who gives you the right?!
你知道我演出过《彭赞斯的海盗》
You know I carried Pirates of Penzance
在Quahog社区剧院上映了一季
that season at Quahog Community Theater.
♪ 我就是!@#$%^&*将军 ♪
♪ I am the (sings gibberish) ...general ♪
♪ !@#$%^&*矿 ♪
♪ (sings gibberish) ...mineral ♪
♪ !@#$%^&*历史 ♪
♪ (sings gibberish) ...historical ♪
♪ !@#$%^&*还有蛋在上面 ♪
♪ (sings gibberish) ...with the eggs on top. ♪
唉 真希望我们能早点到你家
Man, I hope we get back to your house
赶在Patrick行凶之前
before Patrick hurts anyone else!
如果他敢动我家人一根手指头
If he even lays a finger on my family,
我会像揍"谜语人"那样揍他
I'll do to him what I did to the Riddler.
蝙蝠侠中的一个反派角色
砰
蛋蛋*4
不许动 疯子
Freeze, psycho!
哦 Peter 谢天谢地
Oh, Peter, thank God!
Patrick Pewterschmidt 你被逮捕了
Patrick Pewterschmidt, you're under arrest
你涉嫌谋杀 呃…
for the murder of, uh... (bleep)
我不知道那孩子叫什么
I didn't get the kid's name.
我们真应该弄清楚
We're supposed to do that.
Lois 你叫警察来的
Lois, you called the cops?
Patrick 你是我哥哥 我爱你 但你不是好人
Patrick, you're my brother and I love you, but you're not well.
可我现在好多了
But I'm better now.
我已经跟过去决裂了
I've put my past behind me.
省省吧 Patrick
Save it, Patrick.
我们都知道你从精神病院逃出 杀了…
We know you escaped from the asylum and killed...
Bill 我们现在用"Bill"来指代他
Bill, we'll just call him "Bill" for now.
逃出 我-我没有逃啊
Escaped? I-I didn't escape.
就在今天上午 一位很友善的先生打开了我房间的门
Just this morning, a very nice gentleman opened my cell door
说我可以自由离开了
and said I was free to go.
呵 编的真好 不过没用
Yeah, nice try. That's not how it works.
Patrick舅舅 为什么你要勒死胖人
Uncle Patrick, why do you strangle fat people?
大概是奇怪的恋物癖行为
It's probably a weird fetish thing.
有些罪犯是这样的
Some criminals have 'em.
比如那些过分讲究细节的劫匪
Like those anal-retentive bandits
他们去年抢劫了Quahog银行
who robbed Quahog Bank last year.
听好了 举起手来 举直了
All right, hands in the air! Vertically!
两只胳膊必须互相平行
Both arms should be parallel to each other!
你 把这个袋子里装满干净的 无记号的钞票
You, fill this bag with clean, unmarked bills!
不过首先把那个记事本放好 这样它才能跟
But first fix that notepad so it's at a right angle
你的桌角呈正确的角度
with the corner of your desk!
在桌面上整一整那摞收条
And tap that pile of receipts against a flat surface
这样它们看起来才不会参差不齐
so they're not sticking out haphazardly!
还是这样吧 先别想什么钱了
You know what?! Forget about the money!
没个人都去拿一把扫帚
Everybody grab a broom!
我们把这地方好好打扫一番
We are straightening this place up!
好的 营员们
All right, campers,
在胖子扼杀者被抓到之前
until the Fat Guy Strangler is caught,
每个人都得呆在自己屋里
everyone has to stay inside their cabins.
现在我要清点一下人数
Now I'm gonna do a stomach count.
当我叫到你的名字 请回答
When I call your name, please respond.
Jenkins?
(stomach growls)
Robertson?
Davis?
(stomach growls) Elliot?
Elliot上哪儿去了
Where's Elliot?
我看他在睡觉吧
I think he's asleep.
Elliot Elliot 醒醒
Elliot? Elliot, wake up.
Elliot?
我是Swanson警官
Officer Swanson here.
什么 我的天呐
What?! Oh, my God!
怎么了 Joe
What is it, Joe?
半小时前又一个营员被勒死了
Another camper was strangled half an hour ago.
可…也就是说…
But... that means...
Patrick不可能是凶手
Patrick can't be the killer.
我就是这么跟你们说的嘛
That's what I was trying to tell you.
收到了 我正在处理
Acknowledged. I'm on it.
Joe 你愿意为营里解决一个争端吗
Joe, would you settle a camp argument?
是"轰炸球"好 还是"躲避球"好
Is it "Bombardment" or "Dodgeball"?
bombardment是躲避球的一种升级版
会使用3种不同的球
躲避球
Dodgeball.
啊 你还是不懂
Ah, you don't know.
好吧 我还是发布全境通告
Well, I'd better put out an APB
到附近的各个城镇
to all the neighboring towns.
呃 杀手不会离开减肥营的
Oh, the murderer won't leave the camp.
什么 你刚才说什么
What? What are you talking about?
他在"进食"
He's "feeding."
他杀了两个人 而且会再杀人
He killed twice and he's gonna do it again.
他在那儿有许多地方可以藏身
He's got plenty of places to hide out there
也有数量充足受害者可以下手
and a fully stocked corral of victims.
你怎么知道
How do you know that?
相信我 我懂的
Trust me. I know.
其实 Joe 说不定Patrick真能帮上忙
You know, Joe, maybe Patrick can actually be of help.
我是说 还有谁更了解那人的想法
I mean, who better to get inside the mind of someone
除非他自己也勒死过胖子 不然怎么想得到
who's strangling fat people than someone who's done it himself?
是啊 给他个机会吧 Joe
Yeah, give him a chance, Joe.
就像我对非主流少年那样
Like I did with scary teenagers.
我曾经很害怕他们 直到我意识到
I used to be afraid of 'em, until I realized
他们只是被误解了
they were just misunderstood.
嗨 死胖子 把你钱包给我
Hey, fat ass, give me your wallet!
我可以给你钱包
I could give you my wallet,
不过我觉得你真正想要的…
but what I think you really want...
是爱
is love.
是真的
It's true!
我要拿走你的鞋
I'm taking your shoes.
可怜的孩子
Poor kid.
其实 最诡异的是
You know, the weirdest thing is
他的床铺很靠近Chris的
his bunk is right next to Chris's.
是啊 还真是侥幸啊
Yeah, that was a close call.
哦 这可不仅是侥幸的问题
Oh, it was more than a close call.
你说过第一个受害者戴着棒球帽
You said the first victim was wearing a baseball cap,
第二个受害者是金发…
this second one is blond...
杀手并不是想杀这个孩子
The killer wasn't trying to murder this kid.
他是想杀Chris
He was trying to murder Chris.
我的天呐
Oh, my God!
为什么有人会想杀Chris
W-Why would anyone want to kill Chris?
我不知道 不过我知道
I don't know, but I do know
他现在的处境十分危险
that he's in a great deal of danger right now.
- 快点 咱们走 - 好的
- Come on. Let's go! - Yeah!
不过稍等 这是咱们最后的机会来玩"抢内裤"游戏了
But wait, this is our last chance to do a panty raid!
吔 减肥营 我们成功了
Yay! Fat camp! We got it!
哦 不 一阵强风
Oh, no, a gust of wind!
你 你在这儿干什么
Wha, what are you doing here?
你让我颜面尽失 Chris Griffin
You dishonored me, Chris Griffin.
没有人可以比我吃更多的热狗
No one has ever eaten more hot dogs than me.
现在你必须去死
Now you must die!
STEWIE：喂 死胖子
STEWIE: Hey, fat ass!
我有好消息(新闻)要告诉你
I got news for you.
世界新闻
The News of the World!
为什么机器人捧着死人
Why does robot hold dead people?!
那是未来还是过去
Is that future or past?!
老天呐 Stewie 你救了我的命
Oh, my God, Stewie, you saved my life!
啊 你也会为我做过同样的事 Chris
Ah, you would've done the same for me, Chris.
关键是 我们都平安无事
The important thing is, we're all gonna be okay.
对吗 大机器人
Right, Giant Robot?
查尔斯·山本…从大胃王冠军
Charles Yamamoto... went from eating champion
变成了冷血杀手
to cold-blooded killer.
谁能想到呢
Who'd have thought?
哦对了 Joe 他就是昨天
Wait a minute, Joe. That's the guy who opened
替我开门 告诉我
the door to my cell yesterday and told me
可以离开精神病院的人
I could leave the asylum.
哈 是那样吗
Huh. Is that right?
好吧 那一切都说得通了
Well, then it all makes sense.
山本想让这事看起来
Yamamoto wanted it to look like
像你自己出逃造成的
you broke out on your own.
那样的话 当他谋杀了Chris
That way, when he murdered Chris,
就必然由你来当替罪羊了
it was a cinch that you would take the blame.
好吧 Patrick 看来我们欠你一个道歉
Well, Patrick, I guess we all owe you an apology.
Patrick?
他去哪儿了
Where did he go?
他刚才还在这儿的
He was just right here.
发生什么了
What happened?!
该死 他肯定已经逃跑了
Damn it! He must've gotten away!
这怎么可能呢
How is that possible?!
我不知道 不过我最好弄成
I don't know, but I'd better make it
搏斗过的样子
look like there was a struggle.
谁向我脸上打一拳
Someone punch me in the face.
我可真是你的好朋友呀
I'm a good friend to you.
Queen的Killer Queen